dmconfidential.com 2010-06-23

# DM Confidential - Home of the Affiliate Newsletter - Privacy Policy

* * *

**Why do you have a Privacy Policy?**   To let you know how we treat identifiable, personal nonpublic information about you.

**Our Privacy Policy**.  In providing services and products to you, we collect certain nonpublic personal information about you. Our policy is to keep this information confidential and strictly safeguarded, and to use or disclose it only as needed to provide services or products to you, as disclosed in this statement or as otherwise required by law. Protecting your privacy is important to us. 

**What Types of Information About Me Do You Collect?  ** We gather various types of information about you when you use or inquire about our products or services, during the account sign up process and throughout your on-going relationship with us. This may include your name, email, address and Web site usage information. We also have records of our communications with you. The Web site usage information we deal with includes cookies, log file and affiliate statistical information. Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

We use persistent session based cookies which are unique per user. These persistent session based cookies are used for site navigation, session state maintenance and tracking user's interests which enhance the experience on our site by providing targeted offers that the user may find more relevant. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users decline the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.

Some of our affiliate partners use cookies on our site (for example, for tracking which affiliated programs users are clicking on). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Cookie and log file information is not tied to personal information except for technical site maintenance problems and is not shared with third parties. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's “help” file.

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We store this information. The emails are for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

**Information We Disclose**.  We do not disclose your email address to any third party marketers. We do not sell your identifiable, personal information to anyone, except as described in this statement. We disclose tracking information, on an anonymous basis, only to our affiliates, to third parties that we hire to help us provide products and services to you, or as otherwise allowed or required by law. Keep in mind, that if you take advantage of an offer from a third party marketer, they may independently send you offers if you give them your personal information. In this case, you should determine such third party marketer’s privacy policy and inform them separately if you wish to decline receiving offers in the future. Keep in mind also, that we use a technology called framing that may place our website URL in your browser window even though you’ll be on another site in the framed page. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**How Is Information About Me Used?  ** We use information about you to provide products and services to you, for tracking your purchases via anonymous identifier from affiliated sites so that we can provide the service. We do not sell personal non-public information about our users to marketers. 

**How can I update my information?**   If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done here <http://www.dmconfidential.com/Contact-US.php>

**How can I opt-out of receiving emails?**   We only send approximately 1 item a week so we don’t clutter up your inbox.  To opt out of the newsletters please see the link in the footer of the email or visit this page <http://www.dmconfidential.com/Unsubscribe.php>

**How We Safeguard Your Information**.  We have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in place that are designed to protect the security and confidentiality of your information. These include confidentiality agreements with companies we hire to help us provide services to you, password-protected user access to our computer files and strict confidentiality policies that apply to all personnel. 

**Changes To The Privacy Policy**.  By registering, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that  dmconfidential.com  privacy policy may change from time to time. We strongly advise our members to check back from time to time. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users [via email] and/or [by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days] We also welcome any feedback from you; please use this form to contact us <http://www.dmconfidential.com/Contact-US.php>
